Poras Collection of Vietnam War Memorabilia 2007.0124
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
Poras Collection of Vietnam War Memorabilia
undated, 1931-2001
2007.0124
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
23.0 Linear feet
Materials from the American Vietnam War era, including American and Vietnamese propaganda, posters from the pro-war and anti-war movements, as well as artifacts from American soldiers who served in the war.
Poras, Joseph.
History
The American military involvement in Vietnam, commonly referred to in the United States as the Vietnam War, was an attempt to prevent the spread of Communism in Southeast Asia and to support the South Vietnamese government’s opposition to the National Liberation Front and the Communist-allied North. North Vietnam received military and financial support from Communist allies China and the Soviet Union; the anti-communist South Vietnam received military and financial support from the United States.
Initially, there was public support for American involvement in Vietnam, with one poll suggesting an 80% approval rating for the war in February 1965. The number of troops deployed to Vietnam escalated in 1965, and by April 1965, one thousand tons of bombs had been dropped by Americans and South Vietnamese on the Viet Cong in the north. By July 1965, the number of draft calls from the United States was doubled to 35,000 new soldiers drafted each month, and in August of the same year, United States President Lyndon B. Johnson signed a law criminalizing the burning of a draft card. As the number of troops (and casualties) in Vietnam increased, anti-war demonstrations become more prevalent, occurring both in American cities as well as internationally. In October 1965, 25,000 Americans marched on Washington, D.C. in support of US intervention in Vietnam. The following month, 35,000 anti-war protestors circle the White House. By April 1967, anti-war protests in New York involved over 200,000 people. Meanwhile, public opinion about the war was still divided, with 70,000 people in New York marching in support of the war the following month.
A turning point in the war occurred on January 31, 1968, as 84,000 Viet Cong guerrillas aided by NVA troops launched the Tet Offensive, attacking a hundred cities and towns throughout South Vietnam. American TV news crews in Vietnam filmed the attack on the US embassy in Saigon, as well as the bloody battle scenes showing American soldiers under fire, along with dead bodies and images of soldiers dying. The graphic footage was shown on the nightly news in the United States, as had never previously been seen before, and heightened the American public’s disapproval of the war.
Anti-war protests in the United States escalated during this time. On April 23, 1968, anti-war protestors at Columbia University seized 5 buildings. Over 200,000 students in New York City refused to go to class on April 27. By August 1968, there had been 221 student protests at 101 US colleges and universities in that year alone. The "Mobilization" peace demonstration on November 15, 1969, drew approximately 250,000 people, making it at the time the largest anti-war protest in American history.
On April 30, 1970, President Nixon announced that American and South Vietnamese troops had entered Cambodia, sparking another wave of protest in the United States against Nixon and the Vietnam War, particularly at colleges and universities in the days following the announcement. On May 4, 1970, National Guardsmen shot and killed four student protestors at Kent State University in Ohio, and injured an additional 9 others. In response to the killings, over 400 colleges and universities across the United States shut down. Nearly 100,000 protesters surrounded various government buildings including the White House and historical monuments. By March 1970, half of Americans polled believe the war to be "morally wrong." Peace negotiations proceeded in Paris, but were not agreed upon until 1973.
The fighting continued for two more years after the United States left Vietnam. Southern Vietnam was weakened not only in military forces but also economically without the United States troops to support them. Eventually the Viet Minh in North Vietnam over took South Vietnam, establishing a communist government.
Scope and Content
The Poras Collection of Vietnam War Memorabilia consists of a wide range of materials from the Vietnam War era. Covering not only the many opinions of the United States during this time, the collection also includes materials from China, Denmark, Germany, Italy, Russia and Vietnam.
The collection includes buttons, photographs, fliers, booklets, pamphlets, posters, comic books, publications, propaganda money, stamps, envelopes, metals, flags, t-shirts, Zippo lighters used by servicemen, political cartoons, leaflets, movies, audio recordings, maps, books, buttons, and stickers collected by Joseph and Linda Poras.
There are no personal papers in this collection.
Arrangement
Series I: Ephemera ( 1931-1986 )
Series II: Artifacts ( n.d, 1968-1975 )
Series III: Publications and Articles on the Vietnam War ( 1961-1972 )
Series IV: Oversized Posters ( n.d., 1960-2001 )
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Music from the Original Sound Track “Jud” (LP 1188)
Why I Oppose the War in Vietnam Martin Luther King Jr. (LP 1189)
Vietnam: With the American Fighting Man. (LP 1190)
Wish You Were Here, Buddy (LP 1191)
Joy to UC: Free Speech Carols (FF 55)
Seize the Time! Elaine Brown (LP 1185)
War and Memory in the Aftermath of Vietnam September 15/December 19, 1987: A Multi-Disciplinary Program of Visual Art, Commissioned Installations, Photography, Film, Video, Literature, Theater, Music and Public Discussions.
Vietnam Behind the Lines: Images from the War 1965 – 1975.
Decade of Protest: Political Posters From the United States, Viet Nam, Cuba 1965 – 1975
Confronting the War Machine: Draft Resistance During the Vietnam War.
Five Women I Love: Bob Hope’s Vietnam Story.
Blacks in America’s Wars: The Shift in Attitudes from the Revolutionary War to Vietnam
After Shock: Poems and Prose From the Vietnam War.
Dr. Spock on Vietnam
As Seen By Both Sides: American and Vietnamese Artists Look at the War.
The People of Vietnam will Triumph! The U.S. Aggressors Will Be Defeated! – A Collection of Chinese Art Works in Support of the Vietnamese People’s Struggle.
A Nation Builds Under Fire
Know Your Enemy – The Viet Cong
Loin Du Vietnam
Ready on Arrival: USS Independence in Vietnam
The Green Berets
To The Shores of Hell
Vietnam A Television History: The Roots of War
Vietnam: Chronicle of a War
Vietnam Home Movies: The True Story of Captain James “Bob” Powell and “The Gunslingers.”
Vietnam Volume 1: The Seeds of Conflict/America Takes Charge
Vietnam Volume 2: The Elusive Enemy/Courage Under Fire
Vietnam Volume 3: The World of Charlie Company/Fire From the Sky
Vietnam Volume 4: Dateline: Saigon/The TET Offensive
Vietnam Volume 5: America Pulls Back/The End of the Road
Vietnam Weapons of The Infantry: Official U.S. Army Training Film
Why Vietnam?
Woodstock: 3 Days of Peace and Music: The Director’s Cut. Vol. 1
Woodstock: 3 Days of Peace and Music: The Director’s Cut. Vol. 2
Acquisition Information
The collection was donated to Archives & Special Collections by Joseph and Linda Poras in November 2007.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to alternative lifestyles, politics and publications. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Anti-War Propaganda.; Artifacts.; Buttons.; Clippings.; Comic Books.; Maps.; Pamphlets.; Photographs.; Postcards.; Posters.; Publications.; Stamps.; Video Recordings.; Vietnam War.; War Propoganda.; War Protests.
- Series I: Ephemera, 1931-1986
  - "Bullet Bags," Vietnamese, 1969 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Clippings, 1967-1971 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Comic Books, Chinese, 1972 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Comic Books, English, 1966-1986 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, English, 1970 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, Richard Nixon, 1970 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Envelopes, 1965-1973 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Fliers, 1954-1975 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Hunting License, Satirical, 1966 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Map of Vietnam Conflict, After 1966 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Medals Literature, 1954-1975 (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Military Booklets, 1963-1969 (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - National Catalog, Joint U.S. Public Affairs Office, 1969 (Box 2:, Folder 13)
  - Pamphlets, 1965-1973 (Box 2:, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, 1954-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 15)
  - Political Cartoons, Chinese, 1954-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 16)
  - Political Cartoons, English, 1966-1970 (Box 2:, Folder 17)
  - Postcards, 1965-1972 (Box 2:, Folder 18)
  - Postcard, John Lenon and Yoko Ono International Billboard Campaign, Germany, 1969 (Box 2:, Folder 19)
  - Postcard, John Lenon and Yoko Ono International Billboard Campaign, Italy, 1969 (Box 2:, Folder 20)
  - Postcards, Russian, 1931, 1934, 1966-1967 (Box 2:, Folder 21)
  - Posters, Chinese, 1965 (Box 2:, Folder 22)
  - Posters, United States Vietnam War Movies, 1967 (Box 8:)
  - Posters, United States Military, 1954-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 23)
  - Poster, Vietnamese, 1967 (Box 2:, Folder 24)
  - POW*MIA Literature, 1954-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 25)
  - Propaganda Cards, English, 1954-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 26)
  - Propaganda Leaflets, Vietnamese, 1967-1968 (Box 2:, Folder 27)
  - Propaganda Leaflet Information, English, 1954-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 28)
  - Propaganda Banknotes, Vietnamese, undated (Box 2:, Folder 29)
  - Propaganda Playing Cards, Vietnamese, undated (Box 2:, Folder 30)
  - Propaganda Postcards, "VC/Mien Nam", undated (Box 2:, Folder 31)
  - Publications, English, 1962-1969 (Box 2:, Folder 32)
  - Publications, German, 1966 (Box 2:, Folder 33)
  - Scrapbook, US Press Coverage Demonstration, 1967 (Box 2:, Folder 34)
  - Stamps, 1954-1975 (Box 2:, Folder 35)
  - Vietnam Summer Working Paper, 1967 (Box 2:, Folder 36)
- Series II: Artifacts, undated, 1968-1975
  - Political Buttons, undated (Box 3:)
  - Star of Khang Chien Medal, undated (Box 3:)
  - Purple Heart Medal, undated (Box 3:)
  - Bronze Star Medal for Meritorious Acheivement in Ground Operations Against Hostile Forces in South Vietnam, undated (Box 3:)
  - Vietnam Service Medal, undated (Box 3:)
  - POW*MIA Sticker, undated (Box 3:)
  - Vietname Vung Tau Zippo Lighter, undated (Box 3:)
  - K.O.T. Pipe Lighter, undated (Box 3:)
  - Vietnam My Tho Zippo Lighter, undated (Box 3:)
  - Pelanne Claude Zippo Lighter, undated (Box 3:)
  - Cloth Map of Indochina, undated (Box 7:)
  - North Vietnamese Victory Banner, undated (Box 3:)
  - T-Shirt: "Visit Vietnam: Fun Capital of the World", undated (Box 3:)
- Series III: Publications and Articles on the Vietnam War, 1961-1972
  - LIFE, 1961 October 27 (Box 4:, Folder 37)
  - LIFE, 1963 October 11 (Box 4:, Folder 38)
  - LIFE, 1964 March 20 (Box 4:, Folder 39)
  - LIFE, 1964 March 27 (Box 4:, Folder 40)
  - LIFE, 1964 April 10 (Box 4:, Folder 41)
  - LIFE, 1964 July 31 (Box 4:, Folder 42)
  - LIFE, 1964 August 14 (Box 4:, Folder 43)
  - LIFE, 1964 August 21 (Box 4:, Folder 44)
  - LIFE, 1964 September 11 (Box 4:, Folder 45)
  - LIFE, 1964 December 4 (Box 4:, Folder 46)
  - LIFE, 1964 December 11 (Box 4:, Folder 47)
  - LIFE, 1965 August 20 (Box 4:, Folder 48)
  - LIFE, 1965 November 5 (Box 4:, Folder 49)
  - LIFE, 1966 January 14 (Box 4:, Folder 50)
  - LIFE, 1966 April 8 (Box 4:, Folder 51)
  - LIFE, 1966 December 9 (Box 5:, Folder 52)
  - LIFE, 1967 April 7 (Box 5:, Folder 53)
  - LIFE, 1967 August 25 (Box 5:, Folder 74)
  - LIFE, 1968 March 22 (Box 5:, Folder 55)
  - LIFE, 1969 October 24 (Box 5:, Folder 56)
  - LIFE, 1970 May 15 (Box 5:, Folder 57)
  - LIFE, 1972 May 12 (Box 5:, Folder 58)
  - LIFE, 1973 January 21 (Box 5:, Folder 59)
  - National Geographic, 1968 December (Box 6:, Folder 64)
  - Paris Match, 1967 May 13 (Box 5:, Folder 61)
  - Paris Match, 1967 December 2 (Box 5:, Folder 62)
  - Der Spiegel, 1968 February 2 (Box 6:, Folder 65)
  - Der Spiegel, 1969 Decemeber 1 (Box 6:, Folder 66)
  - Der Spiegel, 1968 February 2 (Box 6:, Folder 67)
  - Rolling Stone, 1970 April 2 (Box 5:, Folder 62)
  - Rolling Stone, 1972 May 25 (Box 5:, Folder 63)
  - Time, 1967 May 26 (Box 6:, Folder 68)
  - Time, 1967 December 22 (Box 6:, Folder 69)
- Series IV: Oversized Posters, undated, 1960-2001
  - Shock Patrol, 1960 (Folder P1)
  - U.S. Army Recruiting Poster, 1960 (Folder P2)
  - American Imperialism Must Be Driven Out of Southern Vietnam, 1963 (Folder P3)
  - Scramble at Phan Rang, 1963 (Folder P4)
  - Commandos in Vietnam, 1964 (Folder P5)
  - Sin by Silence, 1964 (Folder P6)
  - Operation CIA, 1965 (Folder P7)
  - Civilization American Style, 1966 (Folder P8)
  - I Want You for the US Army, 1966 (Folder P9)
  - Determined to Protect Every Inch of the Fatherland, 1966 (Folder P10)
  - Postal Support for Troops, 1966 (Folder P11)
  - Protect Your Country and Your Work: Boasting Will Benefit the Enemy, 1966 (Folder P12)
  - This Loss is One for All Our People. This Victory is One for Mankind, 1966 (Folder P13)
  - Visit Vietnam, 1966 (Folder P14)
  - You Be Damned!, 1966 (Folder P15)
  - Alan Ginsburg, 1967 (Folder P16)
  - American Gothic, 1967 (Folder P17)
  - And They Will Never Be The Same, 1967 (Folder P18)
  - Avoid Drafts, 1967 (Folder P19)
  - Cry... Two Three the Number of Vietnams..., 1967 (Folder P20)
  - Confront the Warmakers, 1967 (Folder P21)
  - Demonstration Against the War in Vietnam, 1967 (Folder P22)
  - Draft Women First, 1967 (Folder P23)
  - Dragonship, undated (Folder P24)
  - End Bad Breath, 1967 (Folder P25)
  - Exorcise the Pentagon, 1967 (Folder P26)
  - Far from Vietnam (Loin du Vietnam), 1967 (Folder P27)
  - Johnson's "Johnson", 1967 (Folder P28)
  - Join, 1967 (Folder P29)
  - Message for Hanoi, 1967 (Folder P30)
  - Napalm, 1967 (Folder P31)
  - Perimeter Guard, 1967 (Folder P32)
  - Quack, 1967 (Folder P33)
  - The Purple Realm, 1967 (Folder P34)
  - Victory for Vietnam, 1967 (Folder P35)
  - Vietnam Summer 1967 (Folder P36)
  - War is Not Healthy for Children and Other Living Things, 1967 (Folder P37)
  - 2,000 Planes Shot Down, Vietnam Will Win, 1968 (Folder P38)
  - Air Force Flying Hospital, 1968 (Folder P39)
  - Air Support, 1968 (Folder P40)
  - Berrigan Brothers, 1968 (Folder P41)
  - Ceremony of Going to War, 1968 (Folder P42)
  - Checking the Weather? US Air Force Recruiting, 1968 (Folder P43)
  - Cut the Hands of Imperialism, 1968 (Folder P44)
  - Determined to Defeat American Sky Bandits, 1968 (Folder P45)
  - Dark Ages, 1968 (Folder P46)
  - East Germany: Solidarity With Vietnam, 1968 (Folder P47)
  - Execution, 1968 (Folder P48)
  - Fighting to End War, 1968 (Folder P49)
  - Girls Say Yes, 1968 (Folder P50)
  - Green Berets Movie Poster, 1968 (Folder P51)
  - Hey Roll Me Under, 1968 (Folder P52)
  - Joan Baez, 1968 (Folder P53)
  - Join the Army, 1968 (Folder P54)
  - LBJ, 1968 (Folder P55)
  - Letter to Mom From Vietnam, 1968 (Folder P56)
  - Medic Captain Garcia and Mother Superior, 1968 (Folder P57)
  - National Lampoon Poster, 1968 (Folder P58)
  - Navy Recruit Poster, 1968 (Folder P59)
  - Peace, 1968 (Folder P60)
  - Put Your Money Where Your Boys Are, 1968 (Folder P61)
  - Ready to Take Off, 1968 (Folder P62)
  - Rudi Dutschke, 1968 (Folder P63)
  - Sentinal, 1968 (Folder P64)
  - Silent Majority, 1968 (Folder P65)
  - Special Forces Patrol, 1968 (Folder P66)
  - Stop, 1968 (Folder P67)
  - Suppose They Gave A War..., 1968 (Folder P68)
  - Thunderchief Crew, 1968 (Folder P69)
  - Time Out, 1968 (Folder P70)
  - Toronto, 1968 (Folder P71)
  - Uneasy Solitude, 1968 (Folder P72)
  - US Air Force Hospital Plane, 1968 (Folder P73)
  - VD, 1968 (Folder P74)
  - Vietnam, 1968 (Folder P75)
  - Vietnam at War, 1968 (Folder P76)
  - Vietnam Guerra e Pace, 1968 (Folder P77)
  - Vietnam Will Win, 1968 (Folder P78)
  - Week of Solidarity With Vietnam, 1968 (Folder P79)
  - Welcome to Local Board #48, 1968 (Folder P80)
  - Winning Hearts and Minds, 1968 (Folder P81)
  - Women in Limbo, 1968 (Folder P82)
  - Would You Die to Save This Face?, 1968 (Folder P83)
  - Would You Refuse an Old Man?, 1968 (Folder P84)
  - 17e Parallele: Le Vietnam en Guerre, 1969 (Folder P85)
  - American Aggressors, 1969 (Folder P86)
  - Armored Personnel Carrier Patrol, 1969 (Folder P87)
  - Chicken Little, 1969 (Folder P88)
  - Federal Employees Moratorium, 1969 (Folder P89)
  - Fire Support at Plei Djering, 1969 (Folder P90)
  - Hail Hero!, 1969 (Folder P91)
  - I Want You, 1969 (Folder P92)
  - Instant Support, 1969 (Folder P93)
  - Invest Your Son, 1969 (Folder P94)
  - Jerry Rubin, 1969 (Folder P95)
  - March Against Death, 1969 (Folder P96)
  - March Against the War, 1969 (Folder P97)
  - Mend America, 1969 (Folder P98)
  - Mortar Attack, 1969 (Folder P99)
  - My Tho River, 1969 (Folder P100)
  - Nixon and Mai Lai Massacre, 1969 (Folder P101)
  - Nixon's On the Line, 1969 (Folder P102)
  - Oppose, 1969 (Folder P103)
  - Out Now, 1969 (Folder P104)
  - Pray for Peace, 1969 (Folder P105)
  - Reconnaissance, Long Binh, 1969 (Folder P106)
  - Solidarity With Laos, 1969 (Folder P107)
  - Solidarity With Vietnam, 1969 (Folder P108)
  - Someday?, 1969 (Folder P109)
  - Support Our Boys in Vietnam, 1969 (Folder P110)
  - Vietnam, 1969 (Folder P111)
  - Your Tax Dollars at Work, 1969 (Folder P112)
  - A Teach In, 1970 (Folder P113)
  - Black Protest Against the War, 1970 (Folder P114)
  - Cambridge Mass Referendum on Vietnam War, 1970 (Folder P115)
  - Dickie Mass College of Art Printing, 1970 (Folder P116)
  - Don't Worry I Will Help You, 1970 (Folder P117)
  - Down With Imperialism, 1970 (Folder P118)
  - Dove of Peace, 1970 (Folder P119)
  - Hanoi/Kent, 1970 (Folder P120)
  - Have a Heart, 1970 (Folder P121)
  - Ho Chi Mihn, 1970 (Folder P122)
  - Holy Dickies Prayer, 1970 (Folder P123)
  - Saigon Harbor, 1970 (Folder P124)
  - I've Kicked the Habit, 1970 (Folder P125)
  - Let's Have Peace in Vietnam, 1970 (Folder P126)
  - John Lennon, 1970 (Folder P127)
  - Mass College of Art Goya Poster, 1970 (Folder P128)
  - Mass College of Art Pharmacy Poster, 1970 (Folder P129)
  - No Christmas as Usual, 1970 (Folder P130)
  - Peace Finger, 1970 (Folder P131)
  - Peace Needs No Excuse, 1970 (Folder P132)
  - Peace Makers Boston, 1970 (Folder P133)
  - Protesting: Coca Cola Support of War, 1970 (Folder P134)
  - Psychedelic Peace, 1970 (Folder P135)
  - Quote from Hitler, 1970 (Folder P136)
  - Resist War, 1970 (Folder P137)
  - Saigon, 1970 (Folder P138)
  - Saigon Harbor, 1970 (Folder P139)
  - Sam's Finger, 1970 (Folder P140)
  - Stop the War, 1970 (Folder P141)
  - Stop the War Save Children, 1970 (Folder P142)
  - Support Indochina, 1970 (Folder P143)
  - The Draft Board Tells Us, 1970 (Folder P144)
  - The Silent Majority, 1970 (Folder P145)
  - The Vietnam War Continues, 1970 (Folder P146)
  - The White Dove, 1970 (Folder P147)
  - To Vietnam and Back, 1970 (Folder P148)
  - Tribes, 1970 (Folder P149)
  - Vietnam, 1970 (Folder P150)
  - Vietnam Means Death to the Brothers, 1970 (Folder P151)
  - Vietnamization, 1970 (Folder P152)
  - War is Over, 1970 (Folder P153)
  - Withdrawal, 1970 (Folder P154)
  - Bell Heuys Supporting Vietnam Operations, 1971 (Folder P155)
  - Bring Our Brothers Home Now!, 1971 (Folder P156)
  - Dove, 1971 (Folder P157)
  - Getting Out, 1971 (Folder P158)
  - I'd Rather Be Red Than Dead, 1971 (Folder P159)
  - ...Love it More, 1970 (Folder P160)
  - Lt. Calley, 1971 (Folder P161)
  - Moratorium, 1971 (Folder P162)
  - Nixon Tearing the Heart out of Indochina, 1971 (Folder P163)
  - Peace, 1971 (Folder P164)
  - Peace Swirl, 1971 (Folder P165)
  - Quick Reaction, 1971 (Folder P166)
  - Stop War, 1971 (Folder P167)
  - Thanksgiving, 1971 (Folder P168)
  - The Magician, 1971 (Folder P169)
  - The Trooper, 1971 (Folder P170)
  - Together With Vietnam, 1971 (Folder P171)
  - Vietnam the Victor, 1971 (Folder P172)
  - 9,279,295 Tons, 1972 (Folder P173)
  - Chained to Yesterday/Women in Limbo, 1972 (Folder P174)
  - Chico the Gun Fighter, 1972 (Folder P175)
  - Four More Years, 1972 (Folder P176)
  - Join the Army, 1972 (Folder P177)
  - Logistics, 1973 (Folder P178)
  - March Against the War, 1972 (Folder P179)
  - McGovern, 1972 (Folder P180)
  - McGovern for President, 1972 (Folder P181)
  - Old Soldiers Never Die They Just Fade Away, 1972 (Folder P182)
  - Peace In Paris, 1972 (Folder P183)
  - Peace With Honor, 1972 (Folder P184)
  - Ready to Perform Military Service and Protect the Fatherland, 1972 (Folder P185)
  - Sarge!, 1972 (Folder P186)
  - Supporting the Troops, 1972 (Folder P187)
  - The Visitors, 1972 (Folder P188)
  - Tomorrow the War Will End, 1972 (Folder P189)
  - Vietnam Tomb of Militarism, 1972 (Folder P190)
  - Welcome Home Soldier Boys, 1972 (Folder P191)
  - When the Day of Victor Comes, Our Town Will Return to Constructing a Better Country and Making it Bigger and More Beautiful- Ho Chi Minh, 1972 (Folder P192)
  - Where Have All the Flowers Gone?, 1972 (Folder P193)
  - XII Anniversary of the FNL, 1972 (Folder P194)
  - Cut Aid to Thieu, 1973 (Folder P195)
  - Day of Concerns, 1973 (Folder P196)
  - Determined to Be Victorious, 1973 (Folder P197)
  - Drill Instructor, 1973 (Folder P198)
  - Hill 170, 1973 (Folder P199)
  - La Selva de Xanu, 1973 (Folder P200)
  - Marine Prayer, 1973 (Folder P201)
  - Roof-Scape, 1973 (Folder P202)
  - Silent Majority, 1973 (Folder P203)
  - War Almost Over, 1973 (Folder P204)
  - Broken Treaties Vietnam/Native Americans, 1974 (Folder P205)
  - Independence of Cambodia, 1974 (Folder P206)
  - POW MIA, 1974 (Folder P207)
  - Solidarity With the People of Vietnam, 1974 (Folder P208)
  - Build and Defend the New Life, 1975 (Folder P209)
  - Nhung: Una Muchacha de Sigon, 1975 (Folder P210)
  - The War is Over, 1975 (Folder P211)
  - The People of Vietnam Have Won, 1976 (Folder P212)
  - Ho Chi Mihn, 1980 (Folder P213)
  - For a World of Justice and Solidarity 35th Anniversary OSPAAL, 2001 (Folder P214)
  - Celebrate the Great Victory of the Spring and Move Forward Inspirationally, undated (Folder P215)
  - Convoy Cover, undated (Folder P216)
  - Moratorium, undated (Folder P217)
  - North Vietnam: Victory is Ours, undated (Folder P218)
  - Rainy Landing, undated (Folder P219)
  - Red Cross Nurse, undated (Folder P220)
  - Secretary of Defense: John McNamara, undated (Folder P221)
  - To the Men That Served, undated (Folder P222)
  - Uncle Ho Says Victory, Then It Is!, undated (Folder P223)
  - Unity and Success, undated (Folder P224)
  - Untitled, undated (Folder P225)
  - Untitled, undated (Folder P226)
  - Viva Vietnam, undated (Folder P227)
  - War Continues, undated (Folder P228)
  - Way of Life, undated (Folder P229)
  - Welcome to the New Constitution, undated (Folder P230)
  - Who Love Children as Much as Uncle Ho Does? Who Loves Uncle Ho as Much as We Children Do?, undated (Folder P231)